DANG TRUNG HIEU

WEB DEVELOPER



SUMMARY

I am a front-end developer with nearly 1 year of experience using Vue.js and knowledge of React and Spring Boot. I am passionate about programming and want to make a living from it. I am eager to learn and know how to research documentation.

CONTACT INFO

20/1 Tan Khai Street, Wards 4, Tan Binh District, Ho Chi Minh City

**** 0938865826

SKILLS

HTML, CSS, Tailwind CSS, JavaScript, Vue JS, ReactJS, Java, Spring Boot, MySQL, git, Figma

EDUCATIONS

BACHELOR OF MARINE DIESEL ENGINEER
HCM CITY UNIVERSITY OF TRANSPORT

09/2005 - 10/2009

CERTIFICATES

ADVANCED DIPLOMA IN SOFTWARE ENGINEERING

ApTech Computer Education

06/2023 - NOW

The program starts in January 2021 and ends in

EXPERIENCES

FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER

07/2022 - 01/2023

LTV Software Co., Ltd

- Participate in developing the front-end and maintaining projects at the company.

INTERN FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER

05/2022 - 07/2022

LTV Software Co., Ltd

- Work together with the team to build a Material Template Project using VueJS.
- Write a usage guide for project using Markdown and VueJS.
- Technologies used: HTML, SCSS, Tailwind CSS, VueJS 3, Element Plus.
- My responsibilities: Development, Bug fixing.
- Deployment Link for project: https://argon-dashboard-vue3.web.app.
- Deployment link for document: https://argon-dashboard-vue3-docs.firebaseapp.com.

DIGITAL MARKETING SENIOR SPECIALIST

06/2018 - 12/2019

MOA Viêt Nam

- Develop long- and short-term SEO and Social (Face Book Ads) strategies.
- Oversee or manage pay-per-click (PPC) campaigns with search engine marketing (SEM) strategists.
- Collaborate and oversee to produce compelling and high-quality website content, including blog posts, page descriptions, subwebsite.
- Work closely with Web master and IT team to employ customer experience and conversion rate optimisation methods to turn visitors into more active users/lead and to help improve website performance.
- Collaborate with others within the marketing department (as



June 2023, which consists of 4 semesters:

- Building a website with basic features.
- Building a PC game/app.
- Building software used in small and large businesses.
- Building a website and some mobile applications.

social media team, PR) to align and manage SEO strategy, content website and other digital channels.

- Analyzes campaign performance and recommends solutions for performance optimization daily.
- Track key performance indicators (KPIs) weekly, report rankings, and recommend tactics to optimize.
- Company Link: https://moavn.com/

AWARDS & HONORS

SUCCESSFUL PROJECT DEVELOPMENT

10/2018

MOA Việt Nam

Successfully developing an online marketing service team and providing highly competitive service packages.

PERSONAL PROJECTS

BOOK STORE WITH REACT AND SPRINGBOOT

05/2023 - NOW

- To review the Spring Boot and React knowledge learned in school, I am currently trying to build a website for selling books. This project using Spring Boot for the backend and React for the frontend.
- Github: https://github.com/Trung-Hieu-Dev/fullstack-react-and-springboot

View details ☐

VUE 3 MUSIC APP

04/2023 - NOW

- Develop a music streaming website using Vue.js to practice and further improve my skills: VueJS 3, Pinia, Axios, Firebase, veevalidate, vue-i18n, vue-router....
- The functions include: adding, deleting, editing MP3 files, listening to music, login, logout, validation, post comments.
- Deployment link: https://music-store-kappa.vercel.app.
- Github: https://github.com/Trung-Hieu-Dev/vue-music-app

View details ☐